Is it too much to ask for a single reply?
Have some consideration, Ben!
I'm sorry.
It's my fault that I didn't call you.
I'm really, really sorry.
There are plenty of women
who want your husband.
He's handsome,
kind, smart, rich--
So do I just do nothing?
Of course not!
I am Benjamin Santos's wife.
Benjamin...
Come on! I know you know him.
You're his mistress, aren't you?
Are you calling my husband?
No, I'm calling the village patrol
if you don't stop with your accusations!
Come in.
Stay here for now, Caloy.
Mama will be right back, okay?
I just have to talk to Auntie Beth.
Diane, let me remind you,
maybe this time it'll sink in.
You're an idiot, and you've lost it.
What the hell are you planning to do?
I don't know, Beth!
What do you mean you don't know?
How long are you staying here?
Come on, Beth.
Calm down, okay?
I need some time to think.
What? No.
You need to decide now.
This is unbelievable.
You know how crazy your ex is.
Screw that guy!
He can't keep my son away from me!
He hasn't seen
half of what I'm capable of yet.
And even if he finds us here,
I won't give him Caloy.
Wait, Beth!
Calm down.
Who is it?
Beth.
There's a delivery downstairs.
It might be yours.
Oh, all right, thank you.
I'll check it out.
- It's already paid for, right?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hello?
Ben, Ana was here!
What?
She was pulling up when I got downstairs.
What did she say?
She was asking questions.
I didn't say anything.
I lied.
What about Regina?
Ana didn't see her.
Good thing Regina was quiet.
Okay, good.
Ben.
Her coming here means she knows something.
I'll find a way to throw her off.
It's too late. She knows where we are.
How long are you going to hide us here?
I'll figure something out.
I'll take care of this.
So, what now?
I don't know.
J-Just drive!
- Just keep driving!
- Okay, okay, okay, okay!
Are you sure about this?
No.
I'll stay.
No, it's okay, Kat.
I need some time alone.
Eat something.
Order room service.
Don't worry, it's not Ben.
It's my driver. He's almost here.
Attorney Ben?
Yes, I think it was him.
I think it was his car that I saw pass by.
And why would he pass by here?
Does he still have sessions with you?
He does.
Diane, he cannot see you here.
Well, he didn't.
For now.
But you could cross paths in the future.
He won't be happy if he finds out
that we know each other.
And so what?
He doesn't know
I did a loyalty test on him, right?
Ben's very smart.
And you're being paranoid.
Diane, you don't understand.
You're making things
too complicated, Beth.
You shouldn't even be involved
in his life anymore.
Your loyalty test is over.
But our physical therapy sessions
aren't over, Diane.
And we've become friends.
This is different.
Just don't leave the apartment.
What?
Seriously, Beth?
Okay, fine.
You can go out when we have a session.
So I can make sure he won't see you.
That's what we'll do.
Seriously, Beth. You're overthinking this.
No matter what happens,
I hope you get through this.
I will.
Go on.
All right. Let's eat, Ging.
There you go. Dig in.
- We're not leaving!
We're not going anywhere!
Regina, calm down.
I heard you on the phone with Ben.
It was nothing.
We are not going anywhere, understood?
We are not leaving
because Joel's coming back for me here!
- Give that to me.
If you force me, I will run away!
We are not leaving, Regina!
Give me the knife. Let go!
Drop it! Drop the knife!
We're not going anywhere.
Who said we're leaving?
That's not happening.
So we're not leaving?
- No.
Really?
Yes, Regina.
What a mess.
Someone from here
has been calling him.
If you're the only one who lives here,
then you're the one
who's been calling him!
Like I said,
you have the wrong house.
No one named Benjamin lives here.
Yes, miss?
How may I help you?
Where are you?
I'll pick you up.
It's scorching!
God, it's so hot!
Hi, ma'am. Here's your order.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
Miss? Miss?
- Yes?
Four gin and tonics, please.
- Okay. Let me just get that...
Oh, and two whiskey sours.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can you make that
five gin and tonics, please?
And then three mojitos
with less sugar, please.
Oh, can I add more margarita,
please, without ice?
And then follow up on the tequila.
Thank you!
Okay, so that's
five gin and tonics, and one mojito,
and one margarita without ice,
and... sorry?
Three mojitos, less sugar.
Three mojitos, less sugar. Okay. Got that.
- Okay, thank you.
Thank you!
- Excuse me.
Yes?
Where is my order?
Two whiskeys on the rocks.
Two whiskeys on the rocks. Got that, sir.
- Excuse me. Can you clean this up, please?
Yes?
Sorry. I'm so, so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Um...
I'll just get you a complimentary drink.
This is for table 4.
For clearing.
- Table 12 placed an order.
What is it?
Uh...
It's...
four gin and tonics, three mojitos,
and one margarita, no sugar.
Huh? One more time.
It's five gin and tonics,
three mojitos,
and one margarita with no sugar.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Hi, sir. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello?
Ah, yes.
Is this the security
department of Saguil azucarera?
This is Ana, Attorney Ben's wife.
I just want to ask,
has anyone claimed the cell phone
Attorney Ben left behind?
Yes, ma'am.
Really?
Who?
I didn't catch their name,
but they're not from here.
Not a local?
From the neighboring town?
I believe so.
Do you remember what they look like?
Uh...
Is she pretty?
Sexy?
Ma'am, the phone was claimed by a man.
A man?
Uh, okay.
Okay, okay.
Yes, ma'am.
He said he dropped his phone
when a friend
showed him around the azucarera.
Oh, okay. Okay. Thank you.
Your guy got the phone already?
Yes.
He told them he's a visitor.
That he had a friend
who worked at the azucarera.
Okay. How's Regina?
She overheard our conversation earlier.
She threw a fit.
We can't make her leave so easily.
Okay, Mara. I'll leave you in charge.
I won't be able to visit for now.
All right, Ben.
Have you talked to your wife?
Not yet.
Just make sure
she doesn't come back here, Ben.
Since Regina and I can't leave for now.
Okay.
Juancho, you made the wrong order.
No, I didn't, Lucy.
That's exactly what you told me.
Why are you arguing with me?
Why are you yelling?
Because you're making it so complicated!
Hey, hey, hey! What's happening here?
What's going on?
Your bartender made the wrong order
and refuses to own up to his mistake.
I just did what she said.
- Excuse me?
- Stop it!
Why did you mess up the order?
Ma'am, have I ever messed up
since I started working here?
- You did just now.
- Ma'am!
Come on, just fix this.
The customer is waiting.
Mind you,
that's coming out of your paycheck.
Ma'am!
Ben.
Ana.
Where have you been?
Uh, after my meeting with the client,
Kat and I went out for wine.
What's happening?
I was worried about you.
You weren't picking up.
Happening to... what, exactly?
Well, I'm just... just worried.
Sorry.
Ana, this has never happened.
Something new, huh?
I can be surprising too.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Are you?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Okay. I'm just happy you're home,
and you're safe.
Oops.
Time to go to work, stranger.
There was no confrontation?
Did you even talk about it?
We talked, but I didn't bring up
the phone or that woman.
But why?
I knew he would make up an excuse.
He would just lie.
So what's the point of bringing it up?
I'm worried for you.
My mother told me
to protect my marriage like my life.
Because it is my life.
- And you are.
- But it's so hard.
I always feel like...
every time I'm close
to finding out the truth,
I end up three steps back.
It's like I'm chasing a ghost.
And that is why I'm worried for you.
Why?
What if...
this backfires on you?
If you don't want your pay docked,
don't be an idiot like Juancho!
He messed up a simple order!
Boss, I told you, didn't I?
It's not my fault.
How rude of you to talk back to me.
Because you're throwing me under the bus!
And yeah,
because of that, you are fired!
Don't you ever come back here
because that is your final pay!
Boss, please!
- I don't want to hear it.
- Hey, that's not fair!
Juancho did nothing wrong!
- Excuse me?
- You should fire me!
- If you weren't...
- What?
You're so scared to fire me
because I'm a Saguil?
Well then, fine!
I'll resign myself!
I quit!
Lucy!
Hey, Lucy! Wait!
Are you out of your mind?
Why did you quit?
She didn't even fire you!
I don't want to work in a bar anymore!
Go back there!
It's my decision! Leave me alone!
Well, of course you have no idea
how hard it is to find a job because--
Because I'm a Saguil?
Don't you see
that I'm owning up to my actions?
I quit because it's the only way
to make things right!
Bagasse may be our byproduct,
but it can be something
much more useful for us.
What do you think, Attorney?
Very interesting.
I'm very excited.
Even before your presentation...
...I've been on board.
But, um, just give me more time
to think about it.
Then I'll get back to you.
Okay?
Anything else for today?
- All right.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'll get back to you. Yes.
Thank you.
Yes, Attorney.
I hope you have good news for me.
Elizabeth Valdez.
You and your wife
know this woman, don't you?
I saw her at your party.
Yeah, she's my PT.
Ana is very fond of her.
Why? What did you find?
She's a loyalty tester.
Understood.
Okay.
Thank you, Attorney.
I've got another one. It's blue!
Say,
"Thank you, Auntie Beth!"
You're welcome!
Thanks for all this.
You're too generous.
Back in Manila,
you'd only buy my son
shirts from roadside shops.
Oh, it's nothing.
I don't always get to buy nice things.
So, I make the most of it
while I still can.
Is that why you don't want to go back?
I found an apartment for you and Caloy.
Do you want to check it out?
An apartment?
Can't we just stay here?
Diane...
We still need to be careful.
Ben comes over here once in a while.
Are we going to talk about this again?
Can't you just tell Ben
that we really are friends?
Just don't mention
the loyalty testing part.
You can't hide it forever.
Diane, everything's going well for me now.
You know, a new place, new acquaintances.
I just don't want to ruin
what I have right now.
You get it, right?
Oh, wait. I have to go.
Where are you going now?
I just need to be somewhere.
I'll be back in a bit.
Caloy, see you later!
Bye.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Beth!
Attorney!
What are you doing here?
Attorney... coffee beans.
For you.
Coffee beans?
What's-- What for?
Just to thank you for everything.
Thank you?
Didn't you just treat me and Ana?
But I don't think it was enough.
So, yeah.
Okay. Wow. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This is nice.
Attorney,
I just wanted to ask you something.
Sure.
I think I saw you yesterday.
Me?
Yeah.
Around our area.
I think I saw your car.
This car?
Yes, this car.
Where was I yesterday?
I did some personal errands in town.
And then, I went to the azucarera.
That's all.
Ah...
I'm probably just mistaken.
That's okay.
You know what they say.
When you think
you saw someone who wasn't there,
it means you've been thinking of them.
Or...
they've been thinking of you.
So, which is which?
Maybe I was just
thinking of you, Attorney.
- All right, I'll be on my way.
- Beth.
Why don't I give you a ride?
- But...
- Come on!
You and your son are stupid!
So, Juancho and Lucy are working together?
They're still connected!
My son just works there.
That's another thing!
Why is he working outside?
Is he trying to avoid
his responsibilities here?
He's not avoiding anything.
Just turn me into your slave
instead of him.
Wow, Reynaldo!
You're the most fit person
to do things in this house!
Your son is in perfect condition to--
To what? To be your slave?
Imelda, you don't have the right
to punish my son.
He's innocent.
Just punish me instead.
I'd rather punish your son.
I want him to experience
the hardships
that my children had to go through.
Your Juancho had you at your best
while my Ana and Sam were miserable
without a father.
That's not fair.
Fair?
Now you want to talk fairness? Fine!
Then,
I'll punish both you and your son.
Just wait and see.
Don't leave the house yet.
- I'm on my way home.
Beth?
Attorney?
Seat belt.
T-Thank you.
So, where should we go?
What?
Where should we go?
You said you're going back
to the apartment.
Is that right?
I...
There's somewhere I need to go to first.
Okay.
I'll drive you there, then...
- I'll take you home.
- No.
Hey, Beth.
What's wrong?
No, Attorney, it's just...
You don't have to.
I'll be fine.
No, it's okay.
You're so funny.
Why are you so nervous?
Just relax.
I got you.
I've got some spare time.
Ana isn't home yet.
Ready?
Yeah.
- Juancho.
- Pa.
Why are you home so soon?
Aren't you in the opening shift?
I just got fired, Pa.
Huh? Why? What happened?
Finally!
Good news for today.
You can't spend time
with Mariano's granddaughter anymore.
I'll be in my room.
Excuse me.
Did you have anything to do with this?
Reynaldo,
I can do much worse than that.
But I don't.
Because I don't want
people talking about me
being that evil stepmother.
I hope you're happy now.
No. That's not enough.
Ah, Attorney, thanks for driving me here.
You're most welcome.
I'll wait for you to leave.
No, I'll wait for you to get inside.
Attorney, you don't have to.
My apartment is just a few steps away.
That's the thing, Beth.
You'll never know.
Sometimes,
you think you're already safe,
but suddenly, something bad happens.
You don't have to scare me like that.
No, no. I'm just saying...
always be careful, Beth.
I have a right to my son,
so this isn't kidnapping.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
I think that apartment's better
than the one you showed me before.
But it's still so close to me.
Be honest. You just want me and Caloy
out of here, right?
It's not that. I just thought
if you and Caloy move to Vallente,
Mike might become a bigger problem to you.
Beth, he's trying
to take my son away from me.
If we go back to Manila,
I might never see this kid again.
You're overreacting.
I'm just trying to be nice.
Just admit it.
You want to continue flirting
with that attorney.
And you can't do that with us here.
What are you talking about?
My God.
I saw you smiling outside.
I know what that smile means.
Goodness, Beth.
You know he's married.
That smile meant nothing.
It's not just a smile.
We both know how you are.
The last time you smiled that way,
you were head over heels for a guy.
All right. We'll just leave then.
I'll take that apartment
you were talking about,
so we won't be a nuisance to you.
- Son...
- Diane, wait.
No, it's okay. I get it.
Diane...
There's a newly opened restaurant
on Esplanade Street.
It's my friend Patty's.
Okay.
- Patty?
- Mm-hmm.
Patty...
Who's Patty?
Oh, you haven't met her
because she just got back from the UK.
Let's have dinner there.
Sure.
Of course. Let's go.
Um... are you sure?
If you're busy,
I can just go with Katrina instead.
It's okay.
I always have time for you.
Should I pick you up from the atelier?
No, it's okay.
I have a meeting
with a client in Capistrano,
so I'll just see you there.
It's more efficient.
- Okay.
- I'll get ready for bed.
Okay.
- Good morning.
- Ma'am, Attorney, good morning.
- Morning, Beth.
It's your last PT session today, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay. I'll go ahead.
Don't forget dinner later.
No, I won't.
Ana?
Have a nice day.
- Nanny.
- Ready, Beth?
Yeah.
It's good, but I think there's...
- a bit--
- You feel any pain?
No. A little pinch.
Like, here.
- Here?
- Yeah.
What's the pain level, Attorney?
Uh... it's not too bad.
It's just a bit...
uncomfortable.
- There.
- Here?
Uh, lower.
Here?
Lower.
A little bit to the side.
- Here?
- Can I help you?
Sure.
Here.
It starts here.
Actually, this is affected.
Right here.
There.
This whole muscle.
This whole muscle here, Beth.
Yeah. Because I think...
the pain crawls up here.
From here...
to there.
to here.
Does it hurt?
You're a big help.
I'm going to miss you, Attorney.
I'm going to miss you too.
I'll miss how you help me
heal my shoulders.
I'm going to miss this.
I feel better.
- Y-You feel okay now?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, Beth.
I have to get ready for work.
Hey, thanks again. Okay?
I'll ask the driver to drive you home.
There's no need. I'll be fine.
No, I insist. Okay?
All right. Thank you.
Okay. Thanks again.
Thank you so much, Beth.
Okay.
It'll really catch your attention.
It's a beautiful picture
of Attorney and Ana.
It's really beautiful.
The driver is outside.
He's waiting for you.
Okay, Nanny Cedes, thank you.
I'm going to miss you.
Mm-hmm.
I wish I lived here.
Come on.
Hello, Mara.
Have you talked to your wife?
She's a smart woman, Ben.
Don't worry about it.
I came up with a plan.
Tell me.
I know a way...
to make her stop.
Ben, it's normal for a woman
to have suspicions.
I know.
I'll take care of it.
Just look after my sister, will you?
Don't worry.
Your sister didn't see Ana.
- Hello?
- Hi.
I'm here.
Hi. Oh, no.
My meeting is running late.
Oh, that's okay.
I'll wait for you.
No, I think this will take a while.
I'm so sorry, love.
I think I have to rain check.
Oh, I see. Okay, so...
I'll just see you at home?
Yeah, okay. All right.
I'll see you later, okay? Sorry.
Okay.
Okay, no problem. Bye, I love you.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't you get it?
Now that I canceled our dinner plans,
he'll meet with his mistress.
See? He said he's going home,
but this isn't the way home.
I know what that means.
My question is,
why are you doing that to yourself?
I need to catch them in the act
because that will be my proof
that he's cheating on me!
But you're alone.
Fine, Ana, tell me.
If you see them like how you want,
will you be able to handle it?
I don't know, okay?
I don't know.
I need to catch them in the act.
Please.
Do not do anything that will ruin you.
You shouldn't be doing this to yourself.
You are Ana Madrigal,
for goodness' sake!
Exactly! I am Ana Madrigal!
They can't just make a fool out of me!
Attorney!
Beth.
You're here too?
Yeah.
Oh, Attorney.
You asked me to come here.
What?
Yeah. Yeah, here.
That's you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
So this is why Ana isn't replying.
Oh, I sent it to you.
I'm so sorry.
I wish you had texted me back,
so you wouldn't have bothered to come.
You're silly, Attorney.
I thought you wouldn't have texted me
if you didn't want to hang out.
Right?
Um...
Well, I don't mind fishing with you.
What's that for?
I'll store my catch in here.
I didn't know you could do that.
That thing on top.
To keep the fish from escaping.
That's awesome.
DIY. Cool.
It just needs a rope.
Okay.
Ready.
You're funny, Attorney.
That wasn't mine. I just read it online.
You know what, if Harry, my brother,
hears your joke,
you'll get along well.
You guys have the same humor.
Are you saying I'm corny?
It's okay, you can say it.
No, Attorney. I wish
you could hang out with my siblings.
Because I'm sure
you'd be a good older brother to them.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm.
Yeah, I'd love to meet them.
Fine by me.
I can be there for them.
Really?
Yeah, Beth.
We've grown close.
So your loved ones,
the important people in your life,
are important to me too.
You need these?
Oh, I'm good. Don't worry.
Tch. Okay.
Beth, will you look at me?
Huh?
May I? Just look here.
What's that?
Is that from charcoal?
- Charcoal, Attorney?
- How did that get there?
Were you grilling?
Thank you, Attorney.
Oops. Did you see that?
- Oh! Attorney, come on!
- Did you see that? Go!
Go, go.
I think we got a big one.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Yeah, release it a little.
There.
Just be patient. Just be patient.
It already took your bait.
You got this. You can do it, Beth.
Always remember, Beth,
there are three reasons
why a fish grabs your bait.
Just hold it. Keep it steady.
Number one,
hunger, obviously.
Go. Don't let go. Don't let go.
Two, curiosity. Okay?
Something unfamiliar draws it closer.
Three.
Territory.
Remember that, Beth.
Beth...
Sorry, Attorney. I thought...
Sorry, Attorney. I didn't really mean to.
I'm really sorry.
I'm married, Beth.
I know that.
I'm really sorry, Attorney.
Actually,
I think I'd better go.
No, no, no!
No!
Liar!
He's a liar!
Hey.
Long day?
Yes.
Not too close, Ben.
Okay.
Okay, good night.
That's quite bold of you.
Flirting with a married man.
I didn't mean to fall for your husband.
It just happened.
"Just happened"?
Or did you plan it?
It wasn't planned.
I didn't mean to.
Oh, come on, Beth.
For all I know,
you make moves on clients
you want for yourself.
Didn't you push me to do this?
I've stopped doing
loyalty testing, remember?
Cut to the chase.
You're the one
who put me in this situation.
So it's my fault now?
- Yes.
- You're shameless.
I know.
But you can't hide the fact
that you're the one
who pushed us together.
So if there's anyone to blame,
it's no one but you.
Go on!
Go on.
Do it.
And I'll tell Ben everything you did.
Because between us two, you, Ana...
are the loser.
She's a loyalty tester.
Loyalty tester?
These people are hired to check
if their partners are loyal to them.
That's a job?
Yes.
It's an online thing.
I'm having people trace
Elizabeth and Diane's online accounts.
And a viral video of a man popped up.
"She's a loyalty tester
my girlfriend hired to flirt with me..."
His name is Ryan.
He was furious
because of Diane's loyalty check.
Damn you! You slut!
You're the criminal!
Wait. So they deceive people?
You could say that.
I spoke to Ryan,
and he wanted to sue Diane for fraud.
However, due to the assault that happened,
I told him that he could also be charged.
So-- Okay.
So, how does the whole thing go?
They will send you an online message.
And then,
they will try to connect.
Hi! I knew you were
the one I saw in suggested friends.
Attorney, hello!
Thank you for accepting.
And they will flirt with you.
Can you give me a ride?
Until you end up saying...
- Attorney!
- ...you are not single.
- Yes?
- Let's get coffee.
If the guy turned them down,
then they passed the test.
They're loyal.
But if they gave in,
then they failed.
Oh, my God!
- Sir!
- I'm so sorry.
- I thought you were my wife. I'm sorry.
- I'm really sorry.
- No. What are you doing here?
- I'm sorry.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
Ana put me on a loyalty test.
Are you cheating on her?
No.
Then she's starting to become suspicious.
Right now, she thinks
there's a woman involved.
But once she realizes that's not the case,
she'll become suspicious of other things.
You need to fix this, Ben.
The skeletons from your past
can be dug up.
And I don't want to be involved, Ben.
Understood.
Okay.
Thank you, Attorney.
Uh, sir.
I just need your signature for these.
I'm going fishing today.
Attorney!
Beth?
Oh! Hi, Beth!
You're here too.
Remember that, Beth.
Remember that.
Problem solved.
It's over.
I hope that's enough to get Ana to stop.
Don't tell me to stop!
You were kissing!
- No!
How am I supposed to take that?
- She kissed me!
It's the same thing!
- Ana! Ana! Ana!
I saw you with her!
Ben! Ben!
- Ma'am! Ma'am, please leave!
Let me in! Miss!
- I need to get inside!
Ma'am, you're not welcome!
Ben!
- Get me out of here!
Regina! What are you doing?
- Imelda!
Get out of my way!
I can't let them team up against Ana!
"Beth, I love you.
I'll leave my wife for you."
Did you hear him say that?
He can't tell me,
because his damn wife
is always hanging around!
Which Bible says you have the right
to someone else's spouse?
Are you finally awake?
You can reach all you want,
but you will never, ever...
touch what's mine.
Okay. Okay.
I'll take it instead.
Come on.
Better me than you.